ŁUKASZ KUPŚ

ABOUT ME

I am a Web Developer with 9 years of experience, focused on Front-end side of the development process. I love creating nice and useful things for the Internet people.

In my spare time I love to read sci-fi books, do some jogging, work on side-projects, write tech articles on personal website or learn how to create my own indie game :)

SKILLS

JavaScript ES6 (experienced)

Vue.js / Vuex (experienced)

Git (experienced)

Unit Testing (Mocha, Chai, Jest) (intermediate)

Express.js (intermediate)

Node.js (intermediate)

Wordpress (intermediate)

PhoneGap / Cordova mobile development (intermediate)

Meteor.js (beginner)

Angular.js 1.x (beginner)

React.js (beginner)

Experienced in working with provided backend services built with Ruby On

Rails, Django or Node.js frameworks.

Working in Agile methodologies.

WORK HISTORY

FRONT-END DEVELOPER AT QCONTACT (REMOTE)

01/2018 - currently

Front-end development of SaaS application for communication. Using Vue.js, WebRTC, SIP, Webpack, Mocha, Chai, Jest, git.

FULL-STACK FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER (REMOTE)

01/2015 - currently

A-Z Web development from UI design phase to the deployment on client's server. Working on side-projects that automate everyday programming tasks. Using Node.js, JavaScript, Vue.js, Express.js, Webpack, Gulp.js, Brunch, Sass, git.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER, INFLUENSTER (REMOTE)

06/2017 - 10/2017

Maintaining company product, rebuilt main application module (search) from Django template based to React.js one.

JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER, ITM BUSINESS SP. Z O.O. (POZNAN)

04/2015 - 04/2017

Maintenance and further development of internal front-end framework, creating web applications and Single Page Apps based on company's product API. Developing mobile applications based on already created web modules. Using JavaScript, jQuery, PhoneGap, Cordova, bits of Angular.js 1.x, git.

WEB DEVELOPER, ITM BUSINESS SP. Z O.O. SP. K. (POZNAN)

10/2013 - 03/2015

Creating Wordpress and custom CMS based websites, development of frontend framework for ERP (SaaS) application. Using JavaScript, Wordpress, git.

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER, WEBRACKETS (POZNAN, REMOTE)

06/2010 - 11/2014

Creating Wordpress-based websites, slicing psd files to templates, front-end development.

EDUCATION

POZNAN UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY (MASTER DEGREE: IT IN BUSINESS PROCESSES)

Thesis title: Development of Content Management System using Meteor.js – a Node.js framework.

POZNAN UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY (ENGINEER DEGREE: COMPUTER SCIENCE)

BsC Thesis title: Implementing personal data generator for testing purposes in Ruby on Rails framework.

OTHER RESOURCES

LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/lukaszkups

GITHUB (CURRENT)

https://github.com/lukaszkups

GITHUB (OLD)

https://github.com/mrmnmly

TWITTER

https://twitter.com/lukaszkups

BLOG

https://lukaszkups.net/notes/

Page | 2 Łukasz Kupś